Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1701, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1701)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1702, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1702)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1703, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1703)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1704, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1704)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1705, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1705)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1706, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1706)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1707, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1707)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1708, 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1708)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1709, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1709)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1710, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1710)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1711, 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1711)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1712, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1712)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1713, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1713)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1714, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1714)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1715, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1715)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1716, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1716)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1717, 1 fragment 07.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1717)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1718, 1 fragment 01.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1718)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1719, 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1719)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1720, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1720)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1721, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1721)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1722, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1722)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1723, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1723)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1724, 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1724)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1725, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1725)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1726, 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1726)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1727, 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1727)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1728, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1728)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1729, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1729)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1730, 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1730)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1731, 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1731)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1732, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1732)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1733, 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1733)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1734, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1734)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1735, 1 fragment 04.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1735)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1736, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1736)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1737, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1737)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1738, 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1738)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1739, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1739)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1740, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1740)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1741, 1 fragment 05.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1741)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1742, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1742)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1743, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1743)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1744, 1 fragment 08.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1744)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1745.01, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1745.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1745.02, 1 fragment 06.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1745.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1746, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1746)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1747, 1 fragment 06.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1747)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1748, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1748)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1749, 1 fragment 06.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1749)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1750, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1750)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1751, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1751)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1752, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1752)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1753, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1753)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1754.01, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1754.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1754.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1754.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1754.03, 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1754.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1754.04, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1754.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1755, 1 fragment (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1755)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1757, 1 fragment 09.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1757)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 123
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1758, 1 fragment 07.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1758)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 124
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1759, 1 fragment 06.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1759)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 125
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1760, 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1760)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 126
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1761, 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1761)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 127
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1762, 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1762)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 128
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1763, 1 fragment 09.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1763)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 129
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1764, 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1764)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 130
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1765, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1765)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 131
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1766, 1 fragment 08.5 x 10.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1766)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 132
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1767, 1 fragment 06.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1767)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 133
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1768, 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1768)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 134
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1769, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1769)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 135
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1770, 1 fragment 06.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1770)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 136
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1771, 1 fragment 06.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1771)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 137
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1772, 1 fragment 08.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1772)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 138
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1773, 1 fragment 08.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1773)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 139
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1774, 1 fragment 06.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1774)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 140
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1775, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1775)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 141
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1776, 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1776)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 142
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1777, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1777)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 143
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1778, 1 fragment 16.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1778)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 144
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1779, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1779)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 145
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1780, 1 fragment 11.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1780)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 146
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1781, 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 35, Item P.NYU inv 1781)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 147
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1782, 1 fragment 13.0 x 17.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1782)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 148
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1783, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1783)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 149
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1784, 1 fragment 05.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1784)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 150
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1785, 1 fragment 01.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1785)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 151
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1786, 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1786)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 152
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1787, 1 fragment 09.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1787)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 153
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1788, 1 fragment 06.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1788)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 154
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1789, 1 fragment 16.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1789)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 155
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1790, 1 fragment 14.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1790)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 156
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1791, 1 fragment 07.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1791)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 157
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1792, 1 fragment 08.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1792)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 158
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1793, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1793)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 159
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1794, 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1794)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 160
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1795, 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1795)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 161
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1796, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1796)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 162
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1797, 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 1797)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 163
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1798, 1 fragment 17.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1798)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 164
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1799, 1 fragment 06.0 x 32.0 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 1799)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 165
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1800, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1800)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 166
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1801, 1 fragment 06.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1801)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 167
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1802, 1 fragment 12.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1802)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 168
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1803, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1803)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 169
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1804, 1 fragment 08.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1804)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 170
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1805, 1 fragment 04.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1805)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 171
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1806, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1806)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 172
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1807, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1807)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 173
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1808, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1808)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 174
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1809, 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1809)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 175
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1810, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1810)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 176
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1811, 1 fragment 16.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1811)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 177
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1812, 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1812)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 178
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1813, 1 fragment 05.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1813)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 179
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1814, 1 fragment 04.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1814)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 180
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1815, 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1815)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 181
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1816, 1 fragment 10.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1816)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 182
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1817, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1817)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 183
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1818, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1818)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 184
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1819, 1 fragment 10.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1819)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 185
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1820, 1 fragment 14.0 x 21.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1820)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 186
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1821, 1 fragment 08.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1821)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 187
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1822, 1 fragment 10.5 x 13.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1822)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 188
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1823, 1 fragment 07.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1823)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 189
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1824, 1 fragment 10.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1824)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 190
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1825, 1 fragment 15.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1825)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 191
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1826, 1 fragment 08.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1826)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 192
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1827, 1 fragment 12.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1827)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 193
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1828, 1 fragment 20.0 x 24.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1828)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 194
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1829, 1 fragment 07.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1829)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 195
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1830, 1 fragment 06.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1830)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 196
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1831, 1 fragment 04.5 x 10.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1831)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 197
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1832, 1 fragment 06.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1832)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 198
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1833, 1 fragment 10.0 x 14.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1833)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 199
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1834, 1 fragment 11.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1834)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 200
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1835, 1 fragment 07.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1835)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 201
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1836, 1 fragment 08.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1836)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 202
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1837, 1 fragment 18.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1837)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 203
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1838, 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1838)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 204
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1839, 1 fragment 08.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1839)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 205
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1840, 1 fragment 06.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1840)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 206
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1841, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1841)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 207
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1842, 1 fragment 10.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1842)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 208
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1843, 1 fragment 12.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1843)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 209
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1844, 1 fragment 12.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1844)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 210
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1845, 1 fragment 07.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1845)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 211
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1846, 1 fragment 18.0 x 18.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1846)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 212
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1847, 1 fragment 19.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1847)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 213
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1848, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1848)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 214
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1849, 1 fragment 07.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1849)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 215
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1850, 1 fragment 24.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1850)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 216
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1851, 1 fragment 03.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 36, Item P.NYU inv 1851)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 217
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1852, 1 fragment 07.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1852)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 218
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1853, 1 fragment 24.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1853)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 219
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1854, 1 fragment 12.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1854)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 220
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1855, 1 fragment 06.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1855)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 221
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1856, 1 fragment 10.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1856)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 222
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1857, 1 fragment 12.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1857)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 223
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1858, 1 fragment 09.5 x 14.0 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1858)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 224
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1859, 1 fragment 11.5 x 17.5 cm (Box 37, Item P.NYU inv 1859)
  - Blank Papyri Fragments (Box 57)
- Series II. Ostraka, 11.75 linear feet in 10 small flat boxes
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 001 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 001)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 002 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 002)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 003 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 003)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 004 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 004)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 005 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 005)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 007 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 007)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 008 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 008)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 009 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 009)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 010 (Box 46, Item O.NYU inv 010)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 011 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 011)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 012 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 012)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 013 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 013)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 014 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 014)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 015 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 015)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 016 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 016)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 017 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 017)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 018 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 018)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 019 (Box 47, Item O.NYU inv 019)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 020 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 020)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 021 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 021)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 022 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 022)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 023 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 023)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 024 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 024)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 025 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 025)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 026 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 026)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 027 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 027)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 028 (Box 48, Item O.NYU inv 028)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 029 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 029)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 030 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 030)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 031 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 031)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 032 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 032)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 033 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 033)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 034 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 034)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 035 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 035)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 036 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 036)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 037 (Box 49, Item O.NYU inv 037)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 038 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 038)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 039 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 039)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 040 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 040)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 041 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 041)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 042 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 042)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 043 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 043)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 044 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 044)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 045 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 045)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 046 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 046)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 047 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 047)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 048 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 048)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 049 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 049)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 050 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 050)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 051 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 051)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 052 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 052)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 053 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 053)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 054 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 054)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 055 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 055)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 056 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 056)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 057 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 057)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 058 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 058)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 059 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 059)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 060 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 060)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 061 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 061)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 062 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 062)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 063 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 063)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 064 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 064)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 065 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 065)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 066 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 066)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 067 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 067)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 068 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 068)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 069 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 069)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 070 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 070)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 071 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 071)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 072 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 072)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 073 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 073)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 074 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 074)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 075 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 075)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 076 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 076)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 077 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 077)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 078 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 078)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 079 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 079)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 080 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 080)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 081 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 081)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 082 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 082)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 083 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 083)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 084 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 084)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 085 (Box 55, Item O.NYU inv 085)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 086 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 086)